- Yes, obviously.
- All right.
(Sheldon:)Well, given that missing you
is predicated on you leaving...
(Sheldon:)...logic dictates you must leave.
(Leonard:)Yes, okay, but I'm gonna be gone
for three months.
(Leonard:)What if she doesn't miss me that long
and she meets someone else?
(Sheldon:)She does have a short attention span.
- So I can't go.
- Leonard, you may be right.
(Sheldon:)It appears that Penny secretly
wants you in her life...
(Sheldon:)...in a very intimate
and carnal fashion.
- You really think so?
- Of course not.
(Sheldon:)Even in my sleep-deprived state...
(Sheldon:)...I've managed to pull off
another one of my classic pranks.
Buzzinga.
- Oh, Leonard, what time is it?
- Seven a.m. I'm sorry it's early.
(Leonard:)But we're leaving soon
and I needed to talk to you.
(Leonard(making a change):)Okay.